3mints.info 2013-12-03

# 3Mints Host Shared Hosting, Reseller Hosting and Virtual private servers VPS - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors privacy and rights, 3Mints Host has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors and what we do with information that we gather.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which 3Mints Host collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User").

## Privacy

Users' privacy is very important to 3Mints Host. We are committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to 3Mints Host.

## The Information We Collect

3Mints Host collects personally identifiable information from Users through online forms for ordering products and services. We may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. 

## How We Use Information

3Mints Host may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by 3Mints Host and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with 3Mints Host and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. At no time will 3Mints Host's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists. Personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to our business partners without your prior consent, except that we will disclose the information we collect to third parties when, in our good faith judgment, we are obligated to do so under applicable laws.
